Gordon Kidd Teal papers, Inclusive: 1919-1990, undated, Bulk: 1950-1970, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Professional Work, 1919-1984; 3
  - Professional Work: Notes: Taiwan Trip, 1975, undated (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Professional Work: Notes: Texas Academy of Science: Banquet: Introductions, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Professional Work: Outline: Texas Instruments, Incorporated: Activities, 1952-1962 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Professional Work: Outline: “Texas Instruments Research Activities Applicable to Space”, undated (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Professional Work: Pamphlet: “General Studies in Technical Colleges”, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Professional Work: Pamphlet: “Technical Education in Britain”, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Professional Work: Periodical: Bell Telephone System: “A New Bridge Photo-Cell”, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Professional Work: Periodical: Bell Telephone System: “Analysis of Intrinsic Recombination Radiation from Silicon and Germanium”, 1959 January (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Professional Work: Periodical: Bell Telephone System: “Dislocations in Plastic Deformation”, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Professional Work: Periodical: Bell Telephone System: “Influence of Holes and Electrons on Solubility of Lithium in Silicon”, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Professional Work: Periodical: Bell Telephone System: “Interpretation of Alpha-Values in p-n Junction Transistors”, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Professional Work: Periodical: Bell Telephone System: “Interpretation of Engineering Data”, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Professional Work: Periodical: Bell Telephone System: “Microwave Attenuator Materials and their Applications”, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Professional Work: Periodical: Bell Telephone System: “ p-n Junction Theory by the Method of δ-Functions”, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Professional Work: Periodical: Bell Telephone System: “Photo Emission from Avalanche Breakdown in Silicon”, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Professional Work: Periodical: Bell Telephone System: “Photon-Radiative Recombination of Electrons and Holes in Germanium”, 1954 June (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Professional Work: Periodical: Bell Telephone System: “Pressure Dependence of the Resistivity of Silicon”, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Professional Work: Periodical: Bell Telephone System: “Properties of p-n Junction Transistors”, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Professional Work: Periodical: Bell Telephone System: “Silicon Solar Energy Converters”, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Professional Work: Periodical: Bell Telephone System: “Thermally Induced Acceptors in Germanium”, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Professional Work: Periodical: Fortune: “What’s Up —and down- at Texas Instruments”, 1961 November (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Professional Work: Periodical: GSI: The Grapevine, 1970 March-April (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Professional Work: Periodical: Guide to Scientific Instruments, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Professional Work: Periodical: Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers: Parts, Materials and Packaging, 1970 June (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Professional Work: Periodical: Institute of Radio Engineers: Direction, 1960 November (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Professional Work: Periodical: Institute of Radio Engineers: Direction, 1960 December (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Professional Work: Periodical: The American Institute of Chemists: The Chemist, 1972 November (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Professional Work: Periodical: The American Institute of Chemists: The Chemist, 1974 February (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Professional Work: Periodicals: The S-C Marketeer: Pure Silicon Project, 1957 March-April (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Professional Work: Photographic Materials: Crystals, undated (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Professional Work: Photographic Materials: Laboratory Equipment, undated (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Professional Work: Photographic Materials: People, 1931-1932, undated (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Professional Work: Printed Materials: Institute of Radio Engineers: Board of Directors, 1957 April 3- 1959 March 19 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Professional Work: Printed Materials: Institute of Radio Engineers: Board of Directors, 1959 April 27- October 28 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Professional Work: Printed Materials: Institute of Radio Engineers: Board of Directors, 1959 November 17- 1962 March 8 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Professional Work: Printed Materials: Institute of Radio Engineers: General, 1956 March 6- 1957 December 16 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Professional Work: Printed Materials: Institute of Radio Engineers: General, 1958 January 13- 1959 August 1, undated (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Professional Work: Printed Materials: Institute of Radio Engineers: Section Publications Committee, 1958 January 3- 1959 March 3 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Professional Work: Printed Materials: Institute of Radio Engineers: Section Publications Committee, 1959 April 4- 1960 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Professional Work: Printed Materials: Institute of Radio Engineers: Technical Program Committee, 1959 June 15- September 24 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Professional Work: Printed Materials: Institute of Radio Engineers: Technical Program Committee, 1959 November 17- 1961 February 24 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Professional Work: Printed Materials: Southwestern I.R.E. Conference Organization, 1957 July 29- 1959 April 2 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Professional Work: Printed Materials: Southwestern I.R.E. Conference Organization, 1959 April 8-17 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Professional Work: Printed Materials: Southwestern I.R.E. Conference Organization, 1959 October 3- 1961 April 17 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Professional Work: Printed Materials: Southwestern I.R.E. Conference Organization, 1961 December 20- 1962 April 12 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Professional Work: Printed Materials: Taiwan Trip, 1975 June 16- July 14 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Professional Work: Printed Materials: Taiwan Trip, 1975 July 31- August 18 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Professional Work: Printed Materials: Taiwan Trip, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Professional Work: Printed Materials: Texas Instruments, 1952-1962 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Professional Work: Printed Materials: Texas Instruments, 1964-1968, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Professional Work: Program: Addresses at Semiconductor-Components Division Plant: Texas Instruments, Incorporated, 1958 June 23-24 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Professional Work: Program: IEEE Convention: Medal of Honor Banquet: Gordon Kidd Teal, 1968 March 20 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Professional Work: Program: Seventh Annual Southwestern Institute of Radio Engineers Conference and Electronics Show, 1955 February 10-12 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Professional Work: Program: “Symposium on Materials Science and Engineering”: Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Professional Work: Program: The American Institute of Chemists: Golden Anniversary, 1973 May 16-19 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Professional Work: Program: Texas Academy of Science: General, 1954-1960, undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Professional Work: Program: Texas Academy of Science: “Visiting Scientist Program”, 1960-1961 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Professional Work: Program: Texas Academy of Science: “Visiting Scientist Program”, 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Professional Work: Programs: General, 1954-1971 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Professional Work: Recommendations: Biographical Materials: Institute of Radio Engineers: Awards Committee, undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Professional Work: Recommendations: Institute of Radio Engineers: Virgil Bottom, 1960 February (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Professional Work: Recommendations: Institute of Radio Engineers: William Clingman, 1961 August (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Professional Work: Recommendations: Institute of Radio Engineers: P.J. Gomez and Samuel Mims, 1961, undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Professional Work: Recommendations: Institute of Radio Engineers: Richard Petritz, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Professional Work: References: Texas Instruments, undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Professional Work: Report: “Annual Report of the Advisory Council on Scientific Policy, 1961-1962”, 1963 January (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Professional Work: Report: Council of Scientific Societies: Executive Committee: Chairman, 1962 June 5 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Professional Work: Report: Department of Defense: “The Military Application of Transistors”, 1955 June 7 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Professional Work: Report: Institute of Radio Engineers: Awards Committee, 1960 November (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Professional Work: Report: Institute of Radio Engineers: “Electronic Seminar for the Secondary School Teachers of the Dallas Independent School District”, 1957 March (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Professional Work: Report: Margaret Kelleher: “Marketing in Taiwan” (1 of 2), 1975 March (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Professional Work: Report: Margaret Kelleher: “Marketing in Taiwan” (2 of 2), 1975 March (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Professional Work: Report: Maritime Research Advisory Committee: “Proposed Program for Maritime Administration Research”, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Professional Work: Report: “Research for Industry, 1961”, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Professional Work: Report: “Ricerca Scientifica Italia”, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Professional Work: Report: Texas Instruments, Incorporated, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Professional Work: Report: Texas Instruments, Incorporated, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Professional Work: Report: Texas Instruments, Incorporated: “5-Year Technical Plan, Apparatus Division”, 1959 October (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Professional Work: Report: Texas Instruments, Incorporated: “10-Year Plan for Apparatus Division Research and Development Department”, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Professional Work: Report: Texas Instruments, Incorporated: “Bandwidth Compression in Digital Imagery Transmission”, 1960 September (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Professional Work: Report: Texas Instruments, Incorporated: “Bandwidth Compression in Voice Transmission”, 1960 October (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Professional Work: Report: Texas Instruments, Incorporated: College Recruiting, 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Professional Work: Report: Texas Instruments, Incorporated: “Dynamic Fault Tolerance in Cryoelectric Arrays”, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Professional Work: Report: Texas Instruments, Incorporated: Louis Bailey: “Thermoelectric Materials”, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Professional Work: Report: Texas Instruments, Incorporated: “Stratified Solid State Devices Involving the Tunneling Process”, 1961 June 26 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Professional Work: Report: “The Largest Industrial Corporations in the Republic of China”, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Professional Work: Report: “The Robert A. Welch Foundation Annual Report”, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Professional Work: Report: U.S. House of Representatives: “A Bill to Provide a Standard Reference Data System”, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Professional Work: Report: Varian Associates, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Professional Work: Report: Wright Air Development Division: “Aerospace Electronic Components” (1 of 2), undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Professional Work: Report: Wright Air Development Division: “Aerospace Electronic Components” (2 of 2), undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Professional Work: Reports: General, 1959 June 1- 1960 February 17 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Awards, 1959-1990; 4
  General condition: Excellent.
  This series contains correspondence, certificates, diplomas, and plaques concerning awards that Dr. Gordon Teal and his wife Lyda accumulated over the years from organizations like Baylor University and the Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers. The materials are in excellent condition and have been wrapped in tissue paper for preservation purposes.
  - Certificate: Membership: Baylor University Founder’s Club: Mr. and Mrs. Gordon Teal, 1989 March (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Diploma: Baylor University: Lyda Smith Teal, 1978 March 13 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Honorary Degree: Baylor University: Degree of Laws: Gordon Kidd Teal, 1969 May 30 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Printed Materials: General, 1966-1969 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Printed Materials: General, 1970-1987 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Printed Materials: General, 1990, undated (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Printed Materials: Medal of Honor (1 of 2), 1968 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Printed Materials: Medal of Honor (2 of 2), 1968 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Baylor University: Distinguished Service Plaque: Gordon Kidd Teal, 1965 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Baylor University: Medical Center: Service: Gordon Kidd Teal, 1978 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Baylor University: Outstanding Alumnus: Gordon Kidd Teal, 1965 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Baylor University: Outstanding Alumnus: Gordon Kidd Teal, 1978 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Baylor University: Sigma Pi Sigma: Gordon Kidd Teal, 1959 April 15 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Baylor University: Student Foundation, 1986-1987 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - Baylor University: Trustee Service: Gordon Kidd Teal, 1979 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - Photographic Materials: Banquet: Medal of Honor, 1968 (Box [1072], Folder 1)
  - University of Mary-Hardin Baylor: Century Club, 1988 (Box 14 OVZ, Folder 8)